<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cluster>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[L'action du groupe d'appareils photo japonais Olympus s'écroulait mardi de 29% en séance à la Bourse de Tokyo, après la révélation que le groupe a dissimulé d'importantes pertes sur des titres financiers depuis les années 90.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="460.7372"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="460.8485"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="461.0652"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed 29% in Tuesday session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="461.1766"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed 29% in Tuesday session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="461.8675"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus crumbled Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="462.013"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japanese collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="462.3411"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japanese collapsed 29% in Tuesday session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="462.4351"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="462.537"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has significant hidden losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="462.5464"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="462.5947"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on financial stocks since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="462.6484"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has significant hidden losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="462.6737"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on financial instruments since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="462.6932"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed important losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="462.7061"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on financial stocks since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="462.785"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on financial instruments since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="462.7917"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities from the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="462.8046"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed important losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="462.8651"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed 29% in Tuesday session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has significant hidden losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="462.903"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities from the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="462.9228"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed 29% in Tuesday session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on financial stocks since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="462.9245"><![CDATA[The action of the group of Japanese cameras Olympus collapsed Tuesday from 29% in session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, following the revelation that the group has concealed significant losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="462.9764"><![CDATA[The action of the group of cameras Olympus Japan collapsed 29% in Tuesday session at the Tokyo Stock Exchange, after the revelation that the group has significant hidden losses on securities since the 90s.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Olympus a reconnu que des acquisitions controversées avaient servi à masquer des pertes sur des titres financiers remontant aux années 1980, succombant ainsi à des semaines de pression qui ont fait fondre sa valeur en Bourse de Tokyo.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="426.793"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="427.4925"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="427.6374"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="428.244"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="428.3369"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="428.3585"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="428.7777"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="428.9435"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="429.058"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="429.0883"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="429.2029"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="429.4771"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="429.622"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="429.7878"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="429.8095"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="429.9024"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="430.2287"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="430.3215"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="430.509"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="430.6538"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and that pressure melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="430.7895"><![CDATA[Olympus has recognized that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value in Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="430.9281"><![CDATA[Olympus has acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="431.0048"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its stock value in Tokyo.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="23" total="431.0325"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on the securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure that melts its value Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="24" total="431.073"><![CDATA[Olympus acknowledged that controversial acquisitions had been used to hide losses on securities back to the 1980s, succumbing to weeks and pressure which melts its value in the Tokyo Stock Exchange.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Olympus a dit mardi avoir découvert que des sommes liées à quatre fusions-acquisitions, dont le rachat en 2008 du groupe britannique Gyrus pour 2,2 milliards de dollars, qui a donné lieu à des honoraires anormalement élevés de 687 millions de dollars, avaient servi à dissimuler des pertes sur des titres financiers.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="551.6143"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="552.2631"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high levels of $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="552.6586"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it found that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="552.9316"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had found that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="553.3073"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it found that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high levels of $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="553.3348"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it has discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="553.392"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the purchase in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="553.5804"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had found that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high levels of $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="553.8616"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="553.9836"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it has discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the acquisition in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high levels of $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="554.0408"><![CDATA[Olympus said Tuesday it had discovered that are related to four mergers and acquisitions, including the purchase in 2008 of the British group Gyrus for $ 2.2 billion, which resulted in fees abnormally high levels of $ 687 million, were used to hide losses on securities.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le groupe japonais d'appareils photo Olympus a reconnu mardi avoir maquillé ses comptes pour dissimuler des pertes colossales sur des investissements financiers, aggravant le scandale qui plombe son image et son action en Bourse depuis près d'un mois.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="511.5818"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="511.9485"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="512.0948"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="512.4615"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="512.5885"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="512.631"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="512.7378"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="512.876"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="512.8829"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="512.9551"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="512.9977"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="513.1044"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="513.1287"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="513.1356"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="513.144"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="513.2256"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal that leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="513.2427"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="513.389"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="513.396"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="513.4783"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal that leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="513.4952"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="513.5059"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for almost a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="513.5107"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="23" total="513.6609"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="24" total="513.7386"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal that leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le groupe japonais d'appareils photo, dans le collimateur des marchés depuis l'éviction controversée de son patron le mois dernier, a été forcé d'admettre qu'il avait dissimulé d'importantes pertes sur des investissements financiers depuis les années 1990.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="430.749"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="431.4347"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since 1990.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="432.1237"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, has been forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="432.2455"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="432.5251"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="432.5571"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="432.8094"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, has been forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since 1990.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="432.8227"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="432.9312"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit he had concealed large losses on financial investments since 1990.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="433.2108"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since 1990.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="433.2428"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since 1990.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="433.3506"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the AF market since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="433.5084"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since 1990.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="433.5751"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the crosshairs of the markets since the ouster controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="433.6544"><![CDATA[The Japanese cameras in the collimator markets since the ouster of controversial boss last month, was forced to admit that he had concealed large losses on financial investments since the 1990s.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le groupe d'appareils photo nippon Olympus a reconnu, mardi 8 novembre, avoir maquillé ses comptes pendant des années pour dissimuler des pertes colossales subies à la suite d'investissements financiers, provoquant un énorme scandale au Japon.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="469.6981"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="469.9109"><![CDATA[The group of Japanese cameras Olympus acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="470.6776"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have masked its accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="470.8904"><![CDATA[The group of Japanese cameras Olympus acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have masked its accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="471.1683"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8th, have disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="471.1884"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised its accounts for years to conceal huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="471.3811"><![CDATA[The group of Japanese cameras Olympus acknowledged Tuesday, November 8th, have disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="471.4012"><![CDATA[The group of Japanese cameras Olympus acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised its accounts for years to conceal huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="471.5076"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="471.6862"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised their accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="471.715"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="471.7203"><![CDATA[The group of Japanese cameras Olympus acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="471.9278"><![CDATA[The group of Japanese cameras Olympus acknowledged Tuesday, November 8, have disguised accounts for years to hide huge losses suffered as a result of financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le groupe japonais d'appareils photo Olympus a reconnu mardi avoir maquillé ses comptes pour dissimuler des pertes colossales sur des investissements financiers, aggravant le scandale qui plombe son image et son action en Bourse depuis près d'un mois.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="511.5818"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="511.9485"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="512.0948"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="512.4615"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="512.5885"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="512.631"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="512.7378"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="512.876"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="512.8829"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="512.9551"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="512.9977"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="513.1044"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="513.1287"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="513.1356"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="513.144"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="513.2256"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal that leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="513.2427"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="513.389"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="513.396"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="513.4783"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal that leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="513.4952"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="513.5059"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for almost a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="513.5107"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus has acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, worsening scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="23" total="513.6609"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal beating down his image and share price for nearly a month.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="24" total="513.7386"><![CDATA[The Japanese camera Olympus acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts to conceal huge losses on financial investments, compounding the scandal that leaden image and its share price nearly a month.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le Japon est en ébullition: le groupe d'appareils photo Olympus a reconnu avoir falsifié ses comptes pour dissimuler de grosses pertes.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="268.7079"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to conceal losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="269.4427"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying accounts to conceal losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="269.5201"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to cover large losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="270.2944"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to hide huge losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="270.6429"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to hide big losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="271.0185"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted to falsifying its accounts to conceal losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="271.3119"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to conceal large losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="271.4561"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying accounts to conceal large losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="271.5246"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted to falsifying accounts to conceal losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="271.6741"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to conceal huge losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="271.8183"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying accounts to conceal huge losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="271.8307"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted to falsifying its accounts to cover large losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="272.0095"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus admitted falsifying its accounts to conceal losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="272.0625"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to hide large losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="272.083"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus has admitted falsifying its accounts to cover big losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="272.2311"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus admitted falsifying its accounts to cover large losses.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="272.232"><![CDATA[Japan is in turmoil: the group of cameras Olympus admitted falsifying accounts to conceal losses.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le groupe nippon d'appareils photo Olympus a reconnu mardi avoir maquillé ses comptes pendant des années pour dissimuler des pertes colossales subies sur des investissements financiers, provoquant un énorme scandale au Japon.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="420.1962"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="420.8391"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="420.8715"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that his makeup accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="421.2198"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that makeup accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="421.6865"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts for years to conceal huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="422.1557"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that her makeup accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="422.3294"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts for years to conceal huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="422.3618"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that his makeup accounts for years to conceal huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="422.3756"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that masked its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investment, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="422.4826"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its makeup accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="422.5773"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that its accounts disguised for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="422.7101"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that makeup accounts for years to conceal huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="423.0185"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that disguised its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investment, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="423.0509"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that his makeup accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investment, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="423.2407"><![CDATA[The Japanese group Olympus cameras acknowledged Tuesday that makeup its accounts for years to hide huge losses incurred on financial investments, causing a huge scandal in Japan.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[L'action d'Olympus a perdu 29% à la bourse de Tokyo après de nouvelles révélations : le groupe aurait dissimulé des pertes dans les années 90.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="313.7143"><![CDATA[The action Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations: the group had concealed losses in the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="313.8285"><![CDATA[The action of Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations: the group had concealed losses in the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="315.0873"><![CDATA[The action Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations group had concealed losses in the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="315.2015"><![CDATA[The action of Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations group had concealed losses in the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="315.3372"><![CDATA[The action Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations: the group had hidden losses in the 90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="315.8766"><![CDATA[The action Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations: the group had concealed losses in the '90s.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="315.9908"><![CDATA[The action of Olympus has lost 29% to the Tokyo Stock Exchange after new revelations: the group had concealed losses in the '90s.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
</cluster>