<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cluster>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le procès emblématique de trois cadres politiques du régime khmer rouge au Cambodge s'est ouvert lundi à Phnom Penh, ultime chance pour les victimes de comprendre, plus de 30 ans après, les faits qui ont conduit à la mort de quelque deux millions de personnes.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="452.6869"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="453.0994"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="453.1042"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="453.3766"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="453.4158"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="453.5167"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="453.6978"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, over 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="453.7531"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="453.7939"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="453.8332"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="453.9124"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened in Phnom Penh Monday, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="454.1103"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, over 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="454.1656"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="454.1704"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh, last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="454.3249"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened in Phnom Penh Monday, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="454.3297"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened in Phnom Penh Monday, last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="454.3875"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, over 30 years after the events that led to the death of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="454.4268"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, over 30 years after the events that led to the death of two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="454.4428"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="454.4821"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="454.5829"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh, last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="454.6021"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened in Phnom Penh Monday, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="454.6414"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened in Phnom Penh Monday, last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="23" total="454.7184"><![CDATA[The trial of three iconic political cadres of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened Monday in Phnom Penh last chance for the victims to understand, more than 30 years after the events that led to the deaths of some two million people.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="24" total="454.7422"><![CDATA[The trial of three executives emblematic policies of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia opened in Phnom Penh Monday, last chance for the victims to understand more than 30 years after the events that led to the death of about two million people.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Les trois plus hauts responsables du régime khmer rouge encore en vie ont été accusés lundi de l'une des "pires horreurs" du XXe siècle à l'ouverture de leur procès.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="319.1666"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were accused Monday of one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="319.2203"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday in one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="319.6121"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were accused Monday of one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="319.6658"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday in one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="321.3242"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge alive were accused Monday of one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="321.3779"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge alive were charged Monday in one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="321.4984"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="321.6044"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were accused Monday of one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century to the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="321.6581"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday in one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century to the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="321.7698"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge alive were accused Monday of one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="321.8235"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge alive were charged Monday in one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="321.9439"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="322.0121"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were accused Monday of one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of the trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="322.05"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were accused Monday of one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century to the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="322.0659"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday in one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century with the opening of the trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="322.1037"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday in one of the "horrors" of the twentieth century to the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="322.1416"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were accused Monday of one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century in the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="322.1953"><![CDATA[The three most senior Khmer Rouge still alive were charged Monday in one of the "worst horrors" of the twentieth century in the opening of their trial.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le procès de trois cadres du régime khmer rouge au Cambodge, responsable de la mort de 2 millions de personnes, s'est ouvert lundi à Phnom Penh.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="247.7551"><![CDATA[The trial of three senior Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia, responsible for the deaths of 2 million people, opened Monday in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="248.2096"><![CDATA[The trial of three senior Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia, responsible for the deaths of 2 million people, is open Monday to Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="248.4689"><![CDATA[The trial of three senior Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia, responsible for the death of 2 million people, opened Monday in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="248.9235"><![CDATA[The trial of three senior Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia, responsible for the death of 2 million people, is open Monday to Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Plus de trente ans après la mort de près de deux millions de personnes, le procès emblématique de trois cadres du régime khmer rouge au Cambodge s'est ouvert lundi 21 novembre à Phnom Penh.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="322.9957"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the death of nearly two million people, the trial of three executives emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia is open Monday, November 21 in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="323.6049"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the death of nearly two million people, the trial of three executives emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia is open Monday, Nov. 21 in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="323.7451"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the death of nearly two million people, the trial of three executives emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia opened Monday, November 21 in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="324.5524"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the death of nearly two million people, the trial of three executives emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia opened Monday, Nov. 21 in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="324.938"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the death of nearly two million people, the trial of three executives emblematic of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia is open Monday, November 21 in Phnom Penh.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Plus de trente ans après les faits, l'idéologue du régime khmer rouge Nuon Chea, l'ex-ministre des Affaires étrangères Ieng Sary et le président du Kampuchea démocratique Khieu Samphan doivent répondre à partir d'aujourd'hui devant le tribunal de Phnom Penh parrainé par l'ONU de leurs responsabilités dans les atrocités commises au nom d'une utopie marxiste délirante.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="618.9404"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="619.1194"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="619.393"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, ex-foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="619.4163"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet starting today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="619.5721"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, ex-foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="619.5954"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet starting today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="619.8141"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="619.83"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in court in Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="619.869"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, ex-foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet starting today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="619.952"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="619.9851"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and the President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="619.9932"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="620.009"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in court in Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="620.015"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and the president of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="620.048"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, ex-foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet starting today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="620.0924"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and president of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="620.1509"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="620.1642"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and the President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="620.1941"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and the president of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="620.2715"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and president of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="620.2826"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, ex-foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in court in Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="620.2901"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former foreign minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet starting today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="620.3116"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet starting today in court in Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="23" total="620.33"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologist of Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delusional.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="24" total="620.3794"><![CDATA[More than thirty years after the fact, the ideologue of the Khmer Rouge Nuon Chea, former Foreign Minister Ieng Sary and President of Democratic Kampuchea Khieu Samphan must meet from today in the court of Phnom Penh sponsored by the UN responsibility for the atrocities committed in the name of a Marxist utopia delirious.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Trois anciens leaders des khmers rouges du régime des "champs de la mort" au Cambodge, dans les années 1970, sont finalement jugés en lien avec certaines des pires atrocités du 20e siècle.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="314.7282"><![CDATA[Three former leaders of the Khmer Rouge regime of the "killing fields" in Cambodia in the 1970s, are finally judged in relation to some of the worst atrocities of the 20th century.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
	<sentence>
		<source lang="fr"><![CDATA[Le procès emblématique du régime khmer rouge, qui a fait quelque deux millions de morts dans les années 70, commence véritablement ce lundi 21 novembre 2011.]]></source>
		<target lang="en">
			<nbest id="0" total="281.0196"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="1" total="281.8731"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="2" total="282.7984"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, Nov. 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="3" total="283.4063"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really starts Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="4" total="283.6519"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, Nov. 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="5" total="283.7316"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime, which has some two million died in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="6" total="284.2598"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really starts Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="7" total="284.6314"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really starts Monday, Nov. 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="8" total="284.6709"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, actually begins on Monday 21 November 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="9" total="284.7687"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="10" total="285.2625"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million deaths in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="11" total="285.4849"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really starts Monday, Nov. 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="12" total="285.5104"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime, which has some two million died in the 70s, it really begins Monday, Nov. 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="13" total="285.7794"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, really begins on Monday 21 November 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="14" total="285.8578"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="15" total="286.0107"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, 21 November 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="16" total="286.116"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million deaths in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="17" total="286.1183"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime, which has some two million died in the 70s, it really starts Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="18" total="286.2346"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime, which has around two million died in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="19" total="286.2507"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million died in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="20" total="286.471"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, this really starts Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="21" total="286.4911"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s really began on Monday 21 November 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="22" total="286.5475"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge regime, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really begins Monday, Nov. 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="23" total="286.5738"><![CDATA[The trial emblematic of the Khmer Rouge, which has some two million died in the 70s, it really begins Monday, November 21, 2011.]]></nbest>
			<nbest id="24" total="286.5937"><![CDATA[Landmark trial of the Khmer Rouge, which killed about two million people in the 70s, it really starts Monday, 21 November 2011.]]></nbest>
		</target>
	</sentence>
</cluster>